<xml>
    <infotags>ocpl-specific</infotags>
    <brief>Retrieve information on a single cacheset log entry</brief>
    <issue-id>WRTODO</issue-id>
    <desc>
        <p>Retrieve information on a single cacheset log entry.</p>
    </desc>
    <req name='cslog_uuid'>UUID of the log entry</req>
    <opt name='fields' default='date|user|type|comment'>
        <p>Pipe-separated list of field names which you are interested with.
        Selected fields will be included in the response. See below fot the list
        of available fields.</p>
    </opt>
    <common-format-params/>
    <returns>
        <p>A dictionary of fields you have selected. Currently available fields:</p>

        <ul>
            <li><b>uuid</b> - unique ID of the log entry,</li>
            <li><b>cacheset_uuid</b> - ID of the cacheset which the log entry refers to,</li>
            <li>
                <p><b>date</b> - date and time (ISO 8601) when the log entry was submitted.</p>
                <!--
                PJTODO: Check if the following statement is true or not (and either
                apply of remove this comment).

                <p>Please note that log entries often contain dates only (with the times
                truncated to midnight, as in the local timezone). In such cases, you may
                want to avoid displaying the time. You may assume that if the <b>date</b>
                value contains the "00:00:00" string, then it is date-only.</p>
                -->
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><b>user</b> - a dictionary:</p>
                <ul>
                    <li><b>uuid</b> - ID of the user (author of the log entry),</li>
                    <li><b>username</b> - name of the user,</li>
                    <li><b>profile_url</b> - URL of the profile page of the user,</li>
                </ul>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><b>type</b> - string; log type. One of the values documented
                below.</p>

                <p>Primary types, commonly used:</p>

                <ul>
                    <li>"Has completed" - a user has completed the cacheset.</li>
                    <li>"Comment".</li>
                </ul>

                <p>Types which indicate a change of state of the geocache or confirm the
                state at the given time (used only by some Opencaching installations):</p>

                <ul>
                    <li>
                        "Temporarily unavailable" - log of this type indicates that the status
                        of the cacheset was changed to "Temporarily unavailable" at that time, or it
                        was confirmed as "Temporarily unavailable". Most probably the cacheset was
                        not available to be found at that time, but it was expected to be
                        repaired soon (and then, "Ready to search" log type would be submitted).
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        "Ready to search" - log of this type indicates that the status of this
                        cacheset was changed back to "Available", or it was confirmed as "Available".
                        After some period of not being available the cacheset became ready to be found
                        again.
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        "Archived" - log of this type indicates that the status of this cacheset was
                        changed to "Archived" at this point in time. This usually means that the
                        cache could not be found anymore at this time, and it was not expected to
                        be repaired any time soon.
                    </li>
                </ul>

                <p>Other types (used only by some Opencaching installations):</p>

                <ul>
                    <li>"OC Team comment" - a comment made by the official OC Team
                    member.</li>

                    <li><i>(to be continued)</i> - this list MAY expand in time!
                    Your application should accept unknown log types (you may
                    treat them as "Comment"s).</li>
                </ul>
            </li>
            <li>
                <b>comment</b> - <a href='%OKAPI:docurl:html%'>HTML string</a>, text entered
                with the log entry,
            </li>
        </ul>

        <p>Note, that some fields can change in time (users can edit/delete
        their log entries).</p>

        <p>If given log entry does not exist, the method will
        respond with an HTTP 400 error.</p>
    </returns>
</xml>