<xml>
    <infotags>ocpl-specific</infotags>
    <brief>Retrieve information on a single cacheset</brief>
    <issue-id>WRTODO</issue-id>
    <desc>
        <p>WRTODO</p>
    </desc>
    <req name='path_uuid'>Unique identifier of this cacheset</req>
    <opt name='langpref' default='en'>
        <p>Pipe-separated list of ISO 639-1 language codes. This indicates the
        order of preference in which language will be chosen for fields like
        <b>name</b> and <b>description</b>.</p>

        <p>Please note, that you may also access paths' descriptions in all
        available languages. If you want to do this, you should use fields
        <b>names</b>, <b>descriptions</b> (etc.) instead of <b>name</b> and
        <b>description</b> (etc.).</p>
    </opt>
    <opt name='fields' default='uuid|name|location|type|status'>
        <p>Pipe-separated list of field names which you are interested with.
        Selected fields will be included in the response. See below for the
        list of available fields.</p>
    </opt>
    <common-format-params/>
    <returns>
        <p>A dictionary of fields you have selected. Currently available fields:</p>

        <ul>
            <li><b>uuid</b> - unique ID of the cacheset.</li>
            <li><b>name</b> - name of the cacheset.</li>
            <li>
                <b>names</b> - a dictionary (language code => plain-text string) of
                cacheset names (at this time, there will be only one language,
                but this may change in future).
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><b>location</b> - location of the cacheset in the "lat|lon" format
                (<i>lat</i> and <i>lon</i> are in full degrees with a dot as a decimal point).</p>

                <p>Cachesets consist of many geocaches, so it's usually not possible to
                assign a single, good location to a path. The location returned here
                is the same one we use to display cachesets on the map. It will <i>usually</i>
                point to the center of the area in which the path's geocaches are
                located, but this <b>may</b> change in the future.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><b>type</b> - path type. This might be <b>pretty much everything</b>,
                but there are some predefined types that you might want to treat
                in a special way (separate icons etc.). Primary types include:</p>
                <ul>
                    <li><b>Geodraw</b>,</li> <!-- WRTODO -->
                    <li><b>Touring</b>,</li> <!-- WRTODO -->
                    <li><b>Nature</b>,</li>
                    <li><b>Thematic</b>,</li> <!-- WRTODO -->
                    <li><i>(any other value is valid too)</i></li>
                </ul>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><b>status</b> - path status. Valid cacheset status codes currently include:</p>
                <ul>
                    <li><b>Available</b> - cacheset is available and ready to be WRTODOed,</li>
                    <li><b>Temporarily unavailable</b> - cacheset is currently unavailable
                    (it cannot be WRTODOed) but it will probably be restored soon,</li>
                    <li><b>Archived</b> - cacheset permanently unavailable (moved to the
                    archives).</li>
                </ul>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><b>mentor</b> - dictionary of:</p>
                <ul>
                    <li><b>uuid</b> - cacheset mentor's user ID,</li>
                    <li><b>username</b> - name of the user,</li>
                    <li><b>profile_url</b> - URL of the user profile page.</li>
                </ul>
            </li>
            <li>
                <b>authors</b> - a list of authors. Each element of this list has the same
                structure as the <b>mentor</b> element described above.
            </li>
            <li><b>url</b> - URL of the path's web page.</li>
            <li>
                <b>image_url</b> - an URL of the "main" image of this cacheset (e.g. a logo
                or a photo related to the path's topic), <b>or null</b> if no such photo has
                been assigned.
            </li>
            <li>
                <b>description</b> - <a href='%OKAPI:docurl:html%'>HTML string</a>,
                description of the cacheset.
            </li>
            <li>
                <b>descriptions</b> - a dictionary (language code =&gt;
                <a href='%OKAPI:docurl:html%'>HTML string</a>) of cacheset descriptions.
            </li>
            <li>
                <b>geocaches_total</b> - number of geocaches currently present on this
                cacheset.
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><b>geocaches_found</b> - number of geocaches already found by the
                user.</p>

                <p>You will need Level 3 Authentication to access this field.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><b>geocaches_found_ratio</b> - float, ratio of geocaches already found by
                the user, e.g. <code>0.333333</code> means that the user has found one third
                of the geocaches on this cacheset.</p>

                <p>If <b>geocaches_total</b> is zero, then this ratio will also be zero.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <b>min_founds_to_complete</b> - minimum number of geocaches which a
                user needs to find in order to be eligible to claim this cacheset as
                "completed" WRTODO: or 0 if user has enough founds?
            </li>
            <li>
                <b>min_ratio_to_complete</b> - minimum ratio of found/total geocaches
                which a user needs to have in order to be eligible to claim this cacheset as
                "completed".
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><b>my_completed_status</b> - indicates the status of this cacheset from
                the user's perspective. It has one of the following values:</p>
                <ul>
                    <li><b>not_eligable</b> - if the user has not completed this path,
                    and he didn't find a proper number of its geocaches to be eligable to
                    claim this cacheset as completed,</li>
                    <li><b>eligable</b> - if the user has already found a proper minimum
                    number of geocaches, but he didn't claim the "completed" status yet,</li>
                    <li><b>completed</b> - if the user has (once) found a proper minimum
                    number of geocaches and claimed the "completed" status.</li>
                </ul>

                <p>You will need Level 3 Authentication to access this field.</p>

                <p>Note, that due to possible changes in the number of geocaches and
                the requirements in the minimum number of found caches, the user may end
                up with both the "completed" status, and <b>geocaches_found_ratio</b>
                less than <code>1.0</code>.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <b>completed_count</b> - number of times the path has been successfully
                completed (by all users).
            </li>
            <li>
                <b>last_completed</b> - date and time (ISO 8601) when the
                cacheset has been last completed, <b>or null</b> if it hasn't been yet
                completed by anyone.
            </li>
            <li>
                <b>date_created</b> - date and time (ISO 8601) when the cacheset
                was first published at the Opencaching site.
            </li>
            <li>
                <b>gplog_uuids</b> - list of UUIDs of all log entries of this cacheset.
                The logs are ordered chronologically - latest logs will be on the <i>end</i>
                of this list.
            </li>
        </ul>
    </returns>
</xml>
