<xml>
    <brief>Get information on available logging features</brief>
    <issue-id>TODO</issue-id>
    <desc>
        <p>This method tells which features are available for logging a
        cache or editing a log. You may use it to dynamically disable or
        hide nonfunctional options in a user interface.</p>

        <p>Using this method is <i>always optional</i>. You never need to
        know about differences between OKAPI installations or logging
        preconditions. If a logging feature is not avaible, OKAPI will
        return a user-friendly explanation.</p>
    </desc>
    <req name='reference_item'>
        <p>One of these:</p>
        <ul>
            <li>
                The code of the geocache to be logged. Available features
                for <a href='%OKAPI:methodargref:services/logs/submit%'>services/logs/submit</a>
                will be returned.
            </li>
            <li>
                The UUID of the log entry to be edited. Available features
                for <a href='%OKAPI:methodargref:services/logs/edit%'>services/logs/edit</a>
                will be returned.
            </li>
        </ul>
        <p>The returned values depend on the type and state of the
        geocache, on previous logs and on the OC site. They can change
        any time.</p>
    </req>
    <common-format-params/>
    <returns>
        <p>A dictionary of the following structure:</p>
        <ul>
            <li>
                <p><b>log_types</b> - a list of the log types your user
                can currently submit for the geocache. Available types
                depend on many parameters, like the cache type and state.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><b>can_rate</b> - boolean, <b>true</b> if the user can rate
                the geocache; <b>false</b> if a submitted rating will be ignored.
                Ratings may be disabled for some cache types or for caches
                that the user already rated or owns. Some OC installations do
                not provide ratings.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><b>can_recommend</b> - tells if the user can rate the geocache;
                one of the following:</p>
                <ul>
                    <li>
                        <b>true</b> if the user can add a recommendation for the
                        geocache,
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        <b>need_more_finds</b> if the user needs to find more
                        caches to add a recommendation for the geocache. A
                        submitted recommendation will be ignored,
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        <b>false</b> if the user cannot recommend the cache
                        for some other reason, e.g. the user owns or already
                        recommended the cache. A submitted recommendation
                        will be ignored.
                    </li>
                </ul>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><b>can_set_needs_maintenance</b> - boolean, <b>true</b>
                if the user can set a "needs maintenance" state of the cache by
                submitting <i>needs_maintenance2=true</i>; <b>false</b> if
                this argument will be ignored. This feature is not available
                for all cache types.</p>
            </li>
            <li>
                <p><b>can_reset_needs_maintenance</b> - boolean, <b>true</b>
                if the user can reset a "needs maintenance" state of the cache by
                submitting <i>needs_maintenance2=false</i>; <b>false</b> if
                this argument will be ignored. This feature is not available
                yet at some OC installations.</p>
            </li>
        </ul>
    </returns>
</xml>
