<xml>
	<brief>Get all attribute-related metadata</brief>
	<issue-id>194</issue-id> <!-- WRTODO: renamed from info -->
	<desc>
		This method returns a big chunk of all attribute-related metadata known
		to OKAPI. Usually you will not want to use this method - the result
		might be big enough to make your mobile application slow. Consider using
		one of the other methods in this module.
	</desc>
	<common-format-params/>
	<returns>
		<p>A dictionary of the following structure:</p>
		
		<ul>
			<li>
				<p><b>attributes</b> - a dictionary. Attribute IDs are mapped to
				keys of this dictionary. Each value is a dictionary of the following
				structure:</p>
				
				<ul>
					<li>
						<b>id</b> - string, OKAPI's ID of the attribute (the same as the one
						in the key),
					</li>
					<li>
						<p><b>gs_equivs</b> - a list of Groundspeak (geocaching.com)
						attributes, which have an exact (or very similar) meaning. Each
						attribute is described as a dictionary of the following structure:</p>
						
						<ul>
							<li><b>id</b> - ID of the Groundspeak attribute,</li>
							<li>
								<b>inc</b> - integer, either 1 or 0. See Geocaching.com's
								XSD for details on its meaning,
							</li>
							<li>
								<b>name</b> - the name of the attribute (as it is included
								in Groundspeak's GPX files).
							</li>
						</ul>
						
						<p>Note, that one Groundspeak ID may be present in many gs_equivs.</p>
					</li>
					<li>
						<p><b>internal_ids</b> - a list of internal attribute IDs which
						will be mapped to this attribute when encountered in local
						OC database.</p>
						
						<p>Note, that one internal ID may be mapped to many OKAPI attributes.</p>
					</li>
					<li>
						<p><b>primary_internal_id</b> - the internal ID of the OC site's attribute
						which matches this OKAPI attribute best, or <b>null</b> if there is no
						matching local attribute.</p>
						<p>This field shoud generally NOT be used, because it may not be
						sufficient to completely describe the OKAPI attribute. Use it only if
						your are forced to have a 1:1 mapping of local attributes.</p>
					</li>
					<li>
						<p><b>names</b> - a dictionary of all known names of the attribute,
						in various langauges (ISO 639-1 language code is used as dictionary key).</p>
						
						<p>If you'd like to help with the translations, see
						<a href='https://code.google.com/p/opencaching-api/source/browse/trunk/etc/attributes.xml'>here</a>.</p>
					</li>
					<li>
						<p><b>descriptions</b> - a dictionary of all known descriptions of
						the attribute, in various langauges (ISO 639-1 language code is used
						as dictionary key).</p>
						
						<p>If you'd like to help with the translations, see
						<a href='https://code.google.com/p/opencaching-api/source/browse/trunk/etc/attributes.xml'>here</a>.</p>
					</li>
					<!-- WRTODO: search_inc_captions -->
					<!-- WRTODO: search_exc_captions -->
				</ul>
			</li>
		</ul>
	</returns>
</xml>